♪Come closer♪
اقترب ♪
♪Be more intimate♪
♪ كن أكثر حميمية
♪Tell me if I am tempted♪
♪ قل لي إن كنت أغوى
♪The moment you and I looked at each other♪
♪ في اللحظة التي نظرت فيها أنا وأنت إلى بعضنا البعض
♪We were both tempted♪
كلانا أغوى
♪Remember how shy you were♪
♪ تذكر كم كنت خجولًا ♪
♪That day♪
♪ ذلك اليوم ♪
♪Sweet memories♪
♪ ذكريات حلوة ♪
♪Please be more♪
♪ من فضلك كن اكثر
♪How lucky I am to have you♪
♪ كم أنا محظوظ لوجودك ♪
♪So sweet♪
♪ حلوة جدا ♪
=My Naughty Assistant=
= مساعدي المشاغب =
=Episode 5=
= الحلقة 5 =
I'll pay for your dress.
سأدفع ثمن فستانك.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Xing Enchen.
شينغ اينشين.
Who exactly is she?
من هي بالضبط؟
Why were you being so protective?
لماذا كنت شديد الحماية؟
What I dream of
ما أحلم به
is just others' daily lives.
هي فقط الحياة اليومية للآخرين.
Chen Zifan is quite romantic.
تشن زيفان رومانسي للغاية.
Look, your house was decorated to look so romantic by her.
انظر ، تم تزيين منزلك ليبدو رومانسيًا جدًا من جانبها.
If it weren't for me,
إذا لم يكن الأمر كذلك بالنسبة لي ،
it would be just you two.
سيكون أنتما الاثنان فقط.
I didn't mean it.
لم أقصد ذلك.
But she is just a star.
لكنها مجرد نجمة.
How could she hit me
كيف يمكنها أن تضربني
just because she is a star?
فقط لأنها نجمة؟
You've drunk too much.
لقد شربت كثيرا.
Get dressed.
يرتدى ملابسة.
I'll take you back.
سأعيدك.
I haven't.
ليس لدي.
I was very happy today.
كنت سعيدا جدا اليوم.
I got a slap on my face.
تلقيت صفعة على وجهي.
Come on.
هيا.
Stand up.
الوقوف.
Let's celebrate
دعونا نحتفل
my wonderful day.
يومي الرائع.
It's like a dream.
انها مثل حلم.
(Seems to be quite a shock.)
(يبدو أنها صدمة كبيرة).
Rock,
صخر،
scissors,
مقص،
paper.
ورق.
(Little Lychee.)
(ليتشي ليتشي.)
(I finally find you.)
(أجدك أخيرًا).
♪How many times in my life♪
♪ كم مرة في حياتي ♪
♪I am destined♪
أنا مقدر ♪
♪To meet you and fall in love with you♪
♪ لمقابلتك والوقوع في حبك
♪In my finest age♪
♪ في خيرة عمري ♪
♪How many times in my life♪
♪ كم مرة في حياتي ♪
♪I am destined♪
أنا مقدر ♪
♪To meet you and fall in love with you♪
♪ لمقابلتك والوقوع في حبك
♪In my finest age♪
♪ في خيرة عمري ♪
♪It's a pity♪
♪ إنه لأمر مؤسف
♪That we are not together in this life♪
بأننا لسنا معًا في هذه الحياة
♪But still, thank you♪
♪ لكن مع ذلك ، شكرًا لك ♪
♪For letting me♪
♪ لسماحك لي ♪
♪Walk into your world♪
♪ امش في عالمك ♪